<resources>

    // App name and header picture
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="puerto_vallarta_sign">Puerto Vallarta Sign</string>

    // Beaches Summary text
    <string name="LosMuertos">Probably the most famous, most visited and most popular beaches in town,
        Los Muertos Beach and Olas Altas are located on the south side of the Malecon and Cuale River Island,
        quite a few international hotels and resorts serve as its background, great for people watching,
        families and it’s fine for swimming and other seaside activities.</string>

    <string name="ConchasChinasBeach">Conchas Chinas Beach is, without a doubt, one of the most fascinating
        and striking beaches in downtown Puerto Vallarta, the Banderas Bay area and Mexican beaches in general.
        The melding of various ecosystems in one location, together with its graceful coast and underwater
        profile has given the place a beauty that must be seen to be understood..</string>

    <string name="PlayaCamarones">One of the cleanest and most important tourist beaches in Puerto Vallarta, 
        Camarones Beach (Playa Camarones, “Shrimp Beach”) is a wide piece of clear sand that extends from Villa 
        Premiere to the northern edge of the Malecon in downtown PV. An area that includes dozens of diverse shops, 
        bars and restaurants. Excellent sunbathing beach, you’ll also enjoy the food and drinks at one of the 
        many bars and restaurants that are on the shores of this beach.</string>

    <string name="LasAmapas">This small beach, Las Amapas, is located a little bit south of Viejo Vallarta (Romantic Zone), 
        the area south of the Cuale River in Puerto Vallarta, Jalisco, Mexico. Las Amapas Beach is next to Los 
        Muertos Beach and El Púlpito, the rocky formation, like a peninsula, that sticks out on the south end of 
        Playa Los Muertos in PV.</string>

    <string name="PlayaDestiladeras">It is one of the most popular beaches among the locals, they know it is a wide,
        shallow water beach, something that makes it incredibly kid-friendly. Little by little it’s becoming less of a
        secret and is now also visited by tourists from the US and Canada.</string>

    <string name="PlayaDeOro">Surrounded by an arc of hotels and resorts, you’ll enjoy a variety of recreational activities and water sports
        that include parasailing, water skiing and popular for swimming too. Playa de Oro is one of the many fine beaches in
        Vallarta, both for residents and visitors.</string>

    // Beach Titles
    <string name="LosMuertosTitle">Los Muertos</string>
    <string name="ChinasBeachTitle">Conchas Chinas Beach</string>
    <string name="CamaronesTitle">Playa Camarones</string>
    <string name="AmapasTitle">Las Amapas</string>
    <string name="DestiladerasTitle">Playa Destiladeras</string>
    <string name="OroTitle">Playa de Oro</string>

    // restaurant summary text
    <string name="LosMuertosBrewing">Los Muertos Brewing, Puerto Vallarta’s first craft brewery! Located in the heart of Old
        Town, Los Muertos Brewing is an authentic, cantina style brew-pub serving a variety of artisanal beers including IPA,
        malty ambers, stouts, and even fruit infused ales!</string>
    <string name="laMadalena">Contemporary Mexican restaurant. An innovative fun, avant-garde design, great mixology and
        audiovisual setting.</string>
    <string name="cafeDesArtistes">The Gourmet Tradition of Puerto Vallarta Elegance and exclusive ambiances have placed
        Café des Artistes as an iconic reference of haute cuisine in Puerto Vallarta for over 30 years. The excellence in
        service and high-quality food, make of this restaurant, an ideal venue for intimate celebrations or important business
        reunions.</string>
    <string name="laLecheSummary">We like to reinterpret the culinary tradition irreverently, taking full advantage of local
        products to reinvent the menu every day, making La Leche a fun, delicious and extraordinary space to live together.</string>
    <string name="greenPlaceSummary">Vegetarian and vegan food menu with burgers, salads, sandwiches, plus smoothies and coffee
        drinks. Fully vegan since Jun 2020.</string>
    <string name="casaTradicional">Casa Traditional offers a wide variety of beloved dishes, from hot Molcajetes to Cochinita Pibil,
        Tampiqueña and mouthwatering Carnitas to flawless flan, there is something for everyone! As far as drinks, try our
        refreshing hibiscus margaritas and house made sangria. The ambiance is as colorful and friendly as Mexico itself.</string>

    // restaurant titles
    <string name="LMBTitle">Los Muertos Brewing</string>
    <string name="CasaTradicional">Casa Tradicional \nCocina Mexicana</string>
    <string name="greenPlace">Green Place</string>
    <string name="laLeche">La leche</string>
    <string name="desArtistes">Cafe Des Artistes</string>
    <string name="madalena">La Madalena</string>

    // restaurant addresses
    <string name="losMuertosAddress">Lázaro Cárdenas 302, Zona Romántica, Emiliano Zapata, \n48380 Puerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="madalenaAddress">Av. Francisco Medina Ascencio 2025, Zona Hotelera, Las Glorias, \n48333 Puerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="artistesAddress">Calle Guadalupe Sánchez 740, Centro, 48300 Puerto Vallarta, \nJal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="lecheAddress">Km 2.5, Blvrd Francisco Medina Ascencio, Las Glorias, 48333 \nPuerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="greenAddress">Calle Honduras 309, 5 de Diciembre, 48350 Puerto Vallarta, \nJal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="tradicionalAddress">Calle Zaragoza 245, Proyecto escola, Centro, 48300 \nPuerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>

    // hotel titles
    <string name="tropicon">Tropicon Hotel</string>
    <string name="paramar">The Paramar</string>
    <string name="flamingo">Flamingo Vallarta</string>
    <string name="secrets">Secrets</string>
    <string name="fiesta">Fiesta Inn</string>
    <string name="hacienda">Hacienda \nBuenaventura</string>

    // hotel addresses
    <string name="tropiconAddress">Amapas 214, Zona Romántica, PlayaLos Muertos, \n48380 Puerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="paramarAddress">Paraguay 1272, 5 de Diciembre, 48350 Puerto Vallarta, \nJal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="flamingoAddress">Condomunious Puerto Iguana 136, Isla Iguana, \n48335 Puerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="secretsAddress">David Alfaro Siqueiros 164, Zona Hotelera, Las Glorias, \n48333 Puerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="fiestaAddress">Blvrd Francisco Medina Ascencio 2479-Interior A, \nZona Hotelera Nte., 48333 Puerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>
    <string name="haciendaAddress">Blvrd Francisco Medina Ascencio, Zona Hotelera, \nZona Hotelera Nte., 48310 Puerto Vallarta, Jal., Mexico</string>

    // hotel summary text
    <string name="trpiconHotel">If you’re looking for a family-friendly hotel in Puerto Vallarta, look no further than Tropicana Hotel.
    As your “home away from home,” the hotel rooms offer air conditioning, and getting online is easy, with free internet access available.</string>
    <string name="theParamar">Ideally situated in the centre of Puerto Vallarta, The Paramar provides express check-in and check-out and
        free private parking. Boasting family rooms, this property also provides guests with a terrace.</string>
    <string name="flamingoVallarta">Welcome  to Flamingo Vallarta Hotel and Marina Explore a place filled with life in the heart of theMarina
        Vallarta, minutes away from the best attractions and with the family and business friendly atmosphere that you are looking for.</string>
    <string name="secretsSummary">Romantic. Refined. Remarkable. Located on the golden sand beaches of the Pacific coast within walking distance
        of the famous El Malecon boardwalk, this vibrant oceanfront resort provides adults 24-hour room service, daily refreshed mini-bars,
        entertainment and Unlimited-Luxury.</string>
    <string name="fiestaInnSummary">The hotel is located in the La Isla shopping center. In addition to its 144 guest rooms, the hotel is home
        to the 360° Lounge, where guests will find the B-On business center, La Isla restaurant, and a convenience store and self-service area.</string>
    <string name="haciendaSummary">Enjoy the unique charm of a real Mexican Hacienda surrounded by beautiful gardens, traditional decor and perfect
    facilities for an unforgettable vacation.</string>

    // tours titles
    <string name="zipLine">Outdoor Zip Line Adventure</string>
    <string name="caletasBeach">Las Caletas Beach Hideaway</string>
    <string name="utv">UTV Tours</string>
    <string name="parasailing">Parasailing</string>
    <string name="scubaDive">Scuba Dive at Mariets Islands</string>
    <string name="fishing">Fishing</string>

    // tour summary text
    <string name="zipLineSummary">Rappel down a waterfall, hike through the jungle, ride exhilarating zip lines, and experience our NEW Roller
        Coaster Zipline, all the speed of a zipline with the unique sensation of a roller coaster suspended by cables from the trees. It is
        truly an adventure of a lifetime!</string>
    <string name="caletasBeachSummary">Simply hop on our boat and come with us to the shores of our exclusive and secluded beach hideaway,
        along the Riviera Nayarit and nestled in the Sierra Madre Mountains. Las Caletas, Puerto Vallarta is one of the top four secluded
        tropical beaches in the world—accessible only by boat.</string>
    <string name="utvSummary">On our one-of-a-kind off-road expedition, you will get the chance to hop aboard a Polaris RZR UTV for an exciting
        off-roading tour that takes you across dirt trails and cuts through breathtaking tropical forests located just south of Puerto Vallarta. </string>
    <string name="parasailingSummary">From your secure spot in the sky, you’ll float along on a warm, tropical ocean breeze. While parasailing, you
    may even catch a glimpse of dolphins, manta rays or whales playing in the surf. An exhilarating yet safe trip for the adventurer in all of us.</string>
    <string name="scubaDiveSummary">Travel through these clear waters and see volcanic formations, arches, spires, tunnels, and caves, which create
    the perfect setting for an amazing experience. You’ll see tropical fish, giant manta rays and other creatures that will convince you that the
    Mexican Pacific is a truly amazing place for diving and snorkeling.</string>
    <string name="fishingSummary">Puerto Vallarta fishing is top-notch all year round.  With trophy-size Marlin, Sailfish, Mahi Mahi, and Tuna,
        among many other Sportfish, a Vallarta fisherman seldom goes home empty-handed.</string>

    // layout strings
    <string name="title">title</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="summary">Summary</string>

</resources>